dubaimerc.com 2013-03-24

# DME - Privacy Policy

**Information Collection and Use**

Dubai Mercantile Exchange Limited is the sole owner of the information collected on our site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Dubai Mercantile Exchange Limited collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy, Dubai Mercantile Exchange Limited will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. 

Dubai Mercantile Exchange Limited may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 

  * We have your consent to share the information
  * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested
  * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Dubai Mercantile Exchange Limited to provide a product or service to you
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or
  * We find that your actions on our websites violate the Dubai Mercantile Exchange Limited guidelines 

**Cookies**

We may in the future collect anonymous information from visits to our websites to help us provide better customer service. We may collect the anonymous information through the use of various technologies, including one called 'cookies'. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. 

**Links**

This website contains links to other sites. Dubai Mercantile Exchange Limited is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the Privacy Policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this website. 

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose any information. The information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Other information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. In certain areas, we use encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [info@dubaimerc.com](mailto:info@dubaimerc.com).

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**Questions or Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions, please email to [info@dubaimerc.com](mailto:info@dubaimerc.com).
